<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Audacious Fox</title>
    <link>https://audaciousfox.net/feeds/main.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Audacious Fox</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/feeds/main.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://audaciousfox.net/2016/12/no-mans-sky</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 10:27:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audaciousfox.net/2016/12/no-mans-sky</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;In 1969, the world followed Apollo 11 as it ascended into our atmosphere and transcended our perceived notions of American achievement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the eventual success of that mission, President Nixon was not aloof to the potential for tragedy.  In a speech titled, “In the Event of a Moon Disaster,” Nixon&amp;rsquo;s speechwriter Bill Safire penned the following lines:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In ancient days, men looked at stars and saw their heroes in the constellations. In modern times, we do much the same, but our heroes are epic men of flesh and blood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Others will follow and surely find their way home. Man&amp;rsquo;s search will not be denied. But these men were the first, and they will remain the foremost in our hearts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For every human being who looks up at the moon in the nights to come will know that there is some corner of another world that is forever mankind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which brings me to Hello Games&amp;rsquo; most recent video game, No Man’s Sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are no boxes into which one can put No Man’s Sky (NMS). A mixture of survival and adventure, NMS is fun and frustrating in ways that I’ve never really experienced before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of NMS&amp;rsquo;s most hyped features, the procedural generation of the game world, works as advertised, and you are able to travel from planet surface to space and back without any loading screens. It&amp;rsquo;s not just open world, it&amp;rsquo;s open universe, and I&amp;rsquo;d love to see other games take advantage of this type of technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the luster of procedurally-generated worlds quickly wears off after a few hours. As you explore planet after planet, you realize that the gameplay becomes incredibly repetitive and mundane. There are a quintillion miles of worlds to explore, but the experience on each is only an inch deep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short: You will marvel at parts of NMS, but you will enjoy them much less at its current $60 price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;opening-shot&#34;&gt;Opening Shot&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you launch the game, you&amp;rsquo;re greeted with &lt;code&gt;NO MAN’S SKY&lt;/code&gt; in black against a white background. What I love most about this title is the capital &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; letterform, where the bottom tail of the spine is shorter than the top. Typically, when creating a typeface, the designer will attempt to instill a sense of symmetry, of balance. But this &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;, should it be rendered into a physical form, would most surly topple over.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> New Logo and Identity for Pandora</title>
      <link>https://audaciousfox.net/linked/2016/10/15/pandoras-new-logo</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 10:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audaciousfox.net/linked/2016/10/15/pandoras-new-logo</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Who&amp;rsquo;s had a worse 2016: Donald Trump, the Samsung Galaxy Note 7, or company logos that use serif wordmarks?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> When it Comes to Security Design, Stop Trying to Fix the User</title>
      <link>https://audaciousfox.net/linked/2016/10/15/usable-security</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audaciousfox.net/linked/2016/10/15/usable-security</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier, cybersecurity expert and fellow at the Berkman Center for Internet and Society at Harvard:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The problem isn&amp;rsquo;t the users: it&amp;rsquo;s that we&amp;rsquo;ve designed our computer systems&amp;rsquo; security so badly that we demand the user do all of these counterintuitive things. Why can&amp;rsquo;t users choose easy-to-remember passwords? Why can&amp;rsquo;t they click on links in emails with wild abandon? Why can&amp;rsquo;t they plug a USB stick into a computer without facing a myriad of viruses? Why are we trying to fix the user instead of solving the underlying security problem? [&amp;hellip;]&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must stop trying to fix the user to achieve security. We&amp;rsquo;ll never get there, and research toward those goals just obscures the real problems. Usable security does not mean &amp;ldquo;getting people to do what we want.&amp;rdquo; It means creating security that works, given (or despite) what people do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital security is already a paramount issue in our current world; yet, in practice, &amp;ldquo;usable security&amp;rdquo; is often neither. It&amp;rsquo;s going to take a large amount of educating and designing before users can stay safe despite doing &amp;ldquo;what people do&amp;rdquo; online.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tools and Toys’ Joshua Ginter Reviews the iPhone 7 Plus</title>
      <link>https://audaciousfox.net/linked/2016/10/13/ginter-iphone-7-plus</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://audaciousfox.net/linked/2016/10/13/ginter-iphone-7-plus</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m curious which you find more enjoyable: Mr. Ginter&amp;rsquo;s writing or his product photography. I appreciate his skill in both.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding the review, I was somewhat relieved to see Mr. Ginter reference something I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed on my own iPhone 7:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On occasion, I’ve found the iPhone 7 Plus’ A10 Fusion chip to be too fast for the new home button. iOS will begin to return to the home screen before I can double press the button to bring up the multi-tasking app switcher. It’s not a bad experience at all, it’s just a small downside of the new home button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A small downside for sure, and a flaw I attribute far more to iOS than the new home button engineering. Even double pressing as rapidly as possible on my iPhone 7, the home screen feint is still present, and I&amp;rsquo;d wager a future software update will fix the issue.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>